Guide to the Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, Records SC0541
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Haas Center for Public Service, records
1916-2014
bulk
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University. Haas Center for Public Service
SC0541
162 Linear Feet
These records pertain to the administrative affairs of the Center as well as the various programs sponsored by the Center, including the You Can Made a Difference Conference (YCMAD), the Student Volunteer Network, the Stanford International Development Organization, the Stanford Homelessness Action Coalition, Stanford in Government, Stanford Project on Nutrition, and Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS. Included are correspondence, reports, minutes, agenda, memos, notes, lists, programs, audiotapes, and videotapes. Topics of the YCMAD conferences include hunger, families, racism, the environment, education, health, national security, and urban change. Also included are mounted photographs and captions on the history of public service at Stanford that were exhibited during the opening of the new Haas Center in 1993; and photocopies of minutes and other records from the Chinese Student Club at Stanford, 1916-1953.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The materials were received from the Haas Center for Public Service via administrative transfers, 1998-2017.
Information about Access
Materials in box 15 of accession 1999-252 are restricted until January 1, 2073. Materials in box 18 of accession 2001-237 are restricted until January 1, 2074. Materials in accession 2007-248 are restricted until January 1, 2080. Materials in accession 2008-228 and box 18 of accession 2009-042 are restricted until January 1, 2082. Other materials are open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Arrangement note
Materials are arranged by accession, and as received within each accession.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Stanford Volunteer Network was founded in 1983 to promote public service activities among Stanford faculty, staff, and students. The Network became one of the founding student groups of the Public Service Center, officially established by the University in 1985. In 1989, the Haas family of San Francisco donated $5 million to Stanford University to endow the Public Service Center, which was renamed the Haas Center for Public Service.
Description of the Collection
These records pertain to the administrative affairs of the Center as well as the various programs sponsored by the Center, including the You Can Made a Difference Conference (YCMAD), the Student Volunteer Network, the Stanford International Development Organization, the Stanford Homelessness Action Coalition, Stanford in Government, Stanford Project on Nutrition, and Volunteers Increasing the Visibility of AIDS. Included are correspondence, reports, minutes, agenda, memos, notes, lists, programs, audiotapes, and videotapes. Topics of the YCMAD conferences include hunger, families, racism, the environment, education, health, national security, and urban change. Also included are mounted photographs and captions on the history of public service at Stanford that were exhibited during the opening of the new Haas Center in 1993; and photocopies of minutes and other records from the Chinese Student Club at Stanford, 1916-1953.
Photoprints.; Student volunteers in social service -- California; Voluntarism -- United States; Stanford University. Haas Center for Public Service; Stanford University. Haas Center for Public Service; Chinese Student Club (Stanford University)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1997-279
  - You Can Make a Difference Conferences, Subseries 1
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Entrepreneurs in the Public Interest, 1984
      - Biography on speakers (Box 1, Folder 1-5)
      - Records (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Thank you letters (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Main speakers- morning panel (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Workshop 1-2 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Workshop 3-4 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Workshop 5-6 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Workshop 7-8 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Workshop 9-10 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Workshop 11 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Student notes on workshops (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: World and Local Hunger, 1985
      - Mailing lists (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Conference publicity (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Dorm outreach (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Planning (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Speaker correspondence (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Fundraising (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Student committee minutes (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Steering committee minutes (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Office memos (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Facilities and events logistics (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous records (from binder #1) (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Day 1 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Day 2 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Day 3 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Day 4 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Day 5 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Thank yous (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Follow up (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Cartoon exhibit (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Projects (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous (from binder #2) (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Speaker logistics- general (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Speaker logistics A-Z (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Clippings and misc. records (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Private Initiatives and Public Responsibility, 1986
      - Minutes (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Letters (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Notes (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Executive Committee (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Scheduling (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Participants (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Press (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Dorm outreach (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous (from binder #1) (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - Major speakers (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - Logistics (Box 3, Folder 10)
      - Biographies (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - Workshops (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence- international (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Education (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Environment (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Health Care (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Homeless (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Multi-ethnic (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Peace and Arms conversion (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Technology (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous (from binder #2) (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Families in Transition -- Meeting the Challenges, 1987
      - Program (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Advisory committee (Box 4, Folder 4)
      - Appreciation (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Brochure (Box 4, Folder 6)
      - Committee recruiting (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Lunch (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Panel (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Publicity (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Press (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Registration (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Student meetings (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Advisory committee (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - University departments (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - PSC mailing list (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Student committee (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Community churches (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Pregnancy workshop (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Elderly workshop (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Immigrant families workshop (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Disabilities workshop (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Divorce workshop (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Homeless families workshop (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Working parents workshop (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Family violence workshop (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Third world families workshop (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Poverty workshop (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous information (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - Report: intro. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - Report: news clippings (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - Report: fact sheets (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - Report: volunteer info. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - Report: photos (Box 5, Folder 8)
      - Report: misc. items (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Institutional Racism, 1988
      - Early records (Box 5, Folder 10)
      - Program (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Information (Box 5, Folder 12)
      - Scheavling (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Speaker suggestions (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - RAC/Staff meetings (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Student meetings (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Newsletters (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Budget (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Fundraising letters. (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Invitations (Box 5, Folder 20)
      - Confirmations (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Speaker correspondence (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Travel (Box 5, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Biographies (Box 5, Folder 25)
      - Publicity (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Residential Education (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Panel night (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Cultural night (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Mini panels (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - S.U. workshop (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Higher education panel (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Food faire (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - Sunday service (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - Thank yous (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Evaluations (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Continuing the struggle: a resource guide (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Deciding Our Environmental Future, 1989
      - Publicity (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - Directors' imperatives (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Mailing list (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - Logistics (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Registration (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Budget (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Workshops (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - Program (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Fundraising (1) (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Fundraising (2) (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Student roster (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Issue pack (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Library (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Purchases (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Key contacts and important numbers (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Key people (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Select chairpersons (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - PSC advisory board (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Faculty advisory board (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Students (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Outreach: CSR and RAs (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Atmosphere workshop (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Oceans workshop (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Tropical forests workshop (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Desertification workshop (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Hazardous waste workshop (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Species damage workshop (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Publicity (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Misc. environmental awareness workshops (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Changing Education for a Changing World, 1990
      - Program (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Fundraising (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Program (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Working documents (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Budget (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - Workshops (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Outreach efforts (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Brown bag lunch series (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Conference newsletter (Box 7, Folder 29)
      - Publicity (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - Evaluations (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - Post-conference congratulations (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - Registration list (Box 7, Folder 33)
      - Campus compact letters- D. Kennedy and conference directors (Box 7, Folder 34)
      - Post-conference letter to attendees (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - Conference packet materials (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Health and the Underserved -- Policy Decision, Community Action, 1991
      - Program (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
      - On campus fundraising (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Fall programs (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Health fair (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Off campus publicity (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Media clips (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Speaker information (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Registration (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Off campus fundraising (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - The core committee (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - Faculty/Staff (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - On campus publicity (Box 8, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 15)
      - Workshops (Box 8, Folder 16)
      - Budget (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Opportunities fair (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Evaluation (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Conference program (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Committee lists, budget items (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Selection information (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Applications (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Re-Defining National Security: National Priorities, Community Action, 1992
      - Program (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - On campus fundraising (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Off campus fundraising (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Media (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Advisory board (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Workshops (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Fall programs (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Committee descriptions (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Registration (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Speakers (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Publicity (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Opportunities faire (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous (includes 2 photos) (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Evaluation summary (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous records (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: The University in Transition -- Community Responsibilities and Involvement, 1993
      - Program (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Registration (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Dorm representatives (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Potential speakers (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Financial & Administrative items (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Steering Committee (minutes and agenda) (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Committee records, misc. (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Speaker choices and logistics (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Sample letters (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Conference day (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Literature on speakers (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Literature on topic (Box 10, Folder 1-2)
      - Steering Committee Meetings (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - YCMAD Conference In-House Planners' Manual (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Parent Education Center (East Palo Alto) (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - University - Oakland Metropolitan Forum (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Community Based Education Support Programs in the S.F. Bay Area (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Program (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Speakers - Keynote (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Speakers - Community Panel (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Speakers - Roundtable (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Speakers - Workshops (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Speakers - Regrets (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Speakers - Invitation Letters (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Speakers - Thank you Letters (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Speakers - Correspondence with confirmed Speakers (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Speakers - Permissions for transcripts/videos (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Opportunities Fair (Box 10, Folder 19-21)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Cities in Crisis -- Promoting Urban Change, 1994
      - Program (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Selection for Chair (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Speakers' Committee records (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Speakers' Invitations (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Speaker Arrangements (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Special Fee Application (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous records (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Volunteer Recruitment (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Workshop Contacts (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Publicity: Press Releases and Media Contacts (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Publicity: Posters (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Opportunities Fair (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Nurturing Our Children -- A Renewed Commitment to the Future, 1995
      - Program (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Fundraising: Background and General Information (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Fundraising: Foundations (Contributors) (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Fundraising: Foundations (Non-Contributors) (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Fundraising: Academic Departments (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Fundraising: Foundation Information (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Staff Advisor's Notebook (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Manager's Manual (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - General Planning (Box 12, Folder 3-5)
      - Chairs Notebook: Vision and Recruitment (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Chairs Notebook: Advisory Board (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Chairs Notebook: Organization and Outreach (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Chairs Notebook: Evaluations (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Chairs Notebook: Motivation and Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Throughout the year: Committee Records (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Throughout the year: Children's poetry and art (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous Committee Information (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Day of Conference Committee Records (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Day of Conference Committee Background Materials (Box 13, Folder 2-4)
      - Poster (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Records, Subseries 2
    - How to Survive at Haas: The Official Manual (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - New Building for Haas Center (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Public Service Center (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Audio-Visual Materials, Subseries 3
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference, tape 1 [audiocassette], 1986 Feb 22 (Box 14)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference, tape 2 [audiocassette], 1986 Feb 22 (Box 14)
    - Immigrant Families [audiocassette], 1987 (Box 14)
    - Families in Transition, tape 1 [audiocassette], 1987 Jan 31 (Box 14)
    - Families in Transition, tape 2 [audiocassette], 1987 Jan 31 (Box 14)
    - Panel Discussion [audiocassette], 1987 Nov 14 (Box 14)
    - Closing Remarks [audiocassette], 1987 Nov 14 (Box 14)
    - Daniel Hirsch New Forum, Carmel [audiocassette], 1988 Oct. 17 (Box 14)
    - Perspectives on a Complex System, How Can Change be Effected, tape 1 [audiocassette], 1991 (Box 14)
    - California’s Future: A Universal Health Care Debate [audiocassette], 1991 (Box 14)
    - John D. Rockefeller IV [audiocassette], 1991 (Box 14)
    - Dr. Antonia Novello [audiocassette], 1991 (Box 14)
    - Dr. Woodron Myers [audiocassette], 1991 (Box 14)
    - New Face of Corporate Environmentalism, part 1 [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - New Face of Corporate Environmentalism, part 2 [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - U.S.-Mexico Free Trade [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - Piracy of U.S. Intellectual Property [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - Workshop: Influencing Foreign Policy. Physicians For Social Responsibility [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - Problems of Security and Minorities in Central Europe, Professor Robert Hamilton-Kelly [audiocassette], 1992 Feb 1 (Box 14)
    - You Can Make a Difference '92 National Workshop: Future of CIA... [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - You Can Make an Energy Policy [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - Overcoming Cultural Barriers [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - The Silent Invasion: Controlling Drug Abuse [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - Where Have All The Trees Gone? [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - What Corporate America is Doing for the Family and Workplace [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - When Moffet Falls [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - National Security and The Media [audiocassette], 1992 (Box 14)
    - Monitoring Organizations and Nuclear Safeguards, Dr. Herbert Abrams and Dr. Scott Sagan [audiocassette], 1992 Feb 1 (Box 14)
    - You Can Make a Difference '93 Workshop Academics and Education, S. Friedman and D. Francis [audiocassette], 1993 Apr 24 (Box 14)
    - Volunteerism Plenary [audiocassette], 1993 (Box 14)
    - Repercussions of Univ. Research, You Can Make a Difference (copy) [audiocassette], 1993 (Box 14)
    - You Can Make a Difference: Taking Care of the Community: Issues in Health Care [audiocassette], 1993 Apr 24 (Box 14)
    - Beech St. Blues: An Attempt at Econ. Development [audiocassette], 1993 (Box 14)
    - Worth the Waste? [audiocassette], 1993 (Box 14)
    - Impact of Rodney King Verdict [audiocassette], 1993 (Box 14)
    - Empowering the Homeless [audiocassette], 1993 (Box 14)
    - Beyond Condoms, Angel Fabian, Jonathan Messinger, Donnavan Somera [audiocassette], 1994 Feb 12 (Box 15)
    - It's 1994: Do You Know Where Your Children Are?, tape 1 [audiocassette] (Box 15)
    - It's 1994: Do You Know Where Your Children Are?, tape 2 [audiocassette] (Box 15)
    - Reinvigorating the Economics of Inner Cities, You Can Make a Difference Conference [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Cities in Crisis, Video Presentation Town Meeting, Floyd Tompkins [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - Building Community [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - Crime Control, Joe McNamara, T. Massengale, Gil Tarcetti [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - Reinvigorating the Econ. of Inner Cities, Wkshp A [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - Opportunities for City Youth: A Youthful Perspective [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - A Youthful Perspective [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference Conference: Cities in Crisis -- Welcome Angela Glover and Michael Kirst [audiocassette], 1994 (Box 15)
    - Viederman--Sustainable Society, Friday Night, tape 1 [audiocassette] (Box 15)
    - Viederman--Sustainable Society, Friday Night, tape 2 [audiocassette] (Box 15)
    - U.S./ Mexico Free Trade [microcassette] (Box 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference T.R.T., tape 1 [videocassette], 1994 Feb 12 (Box 15)
    - You Can Make a Difference T.R.T., tape 2 [videocassette], 1994 Feb 12 (Box 15)
  - Memorabilia, Subseries 4
    - "Institutional Racism; The Struggle for Change, A Conference at Stanford University, Nov. 12-15, 1997" [button] (Box 15)
  - Oversize photographs, Subseries 5
    Scope and Contents note
    This subseries consists of oversize mounted photographs from an exhibit during the opening of the new Haas building.
    - Group of Stanford men in various uniforms (C1) (Box 16)
    - Female Stanford students holding suffrage signs (E1) (Box 16)
    - Five female Stanford students in uniform (E2) (Box 16)
    - Five men in uniform outside a Stanford building (F6) (Box 16)
    - Group of students holding signs with anti-Hitler sayings (H3) (Box 16)
    - Male student standing at a podium for a Vietnam rally (H5) (Box 16)
    - Two Stanford students playing basketball with a group of boys (J1) (Box 16)
    - Female Stanford student looking on as a tutee does his work (K4) (Box 16)
    - Anti-Apartheid Campaign (N2) (Box 16)
    - Jane Stanford (unnumbered) (Box 17)
    - Two women standing with a group of children outside the Stanford Free Kindergarten (A3) (Box 17)
    - Poster asking people to donate food for Finland (D2) (Box 17)
    - Stanford students waiting in line at a Dimes for Diplomas booth (F1) (Box 17)
    - Poster"“Co-ordinator to Help Stanford Students.. ." (F3) (Box 17)
    - Stanford men standing in a field wearing gas masks (F4) (Box 17)
    - Two male students holding demonstration signs (G1) (Box 17)
    - Stanford faculty marching in a circle with posters stating “Faculty opposed to political firings” (unnumbered) (Box 17)
    - Male Stanford student teaching in an Asian classroom (I2) (Box 17)
    - Gathering, large hot air balloon (I3) (Box 17)
    - Caption: "A Century of Service." (Box 18)
    - Student Tutoring (J2) (Box 18)
    - Two female students playing a game with four small children at a nursery (K1) (Box 18)
    - Male Stanford student kneeling hugging a young girl (K3) (Box 18)
    - Haas Center for Public Service [in Owen House] (L1) (Box 18)
    - Student dancing at home for elderly (M2) (Box 18)